SUPRAVAT MONDAL

Vill- Bural, P.O-Barjagu, P.S-Sabang, Dist-Paschim Medinipur (W.B)

Cell: +91-9964090958

EMAIL: supravat.com@gmail.com

IT PROFESSIONAL

To learn and function effectively in an organization and be able to deliver to the bottom-line. To constantly upgrade my knowledge and skills and make a difference in whatever I do.

SUMMARY OF SKILLS

A qualified professional with BCA passed 12+ years of experience and currently working as a software developer in Tech Mahindra.

Having well knowledge in PHP and MySql with Magento 1, Magento 2, Laravel, CakePhp, CodeIgniter, Yii.

Having well knowledge in ERP Integration, e-commerce software Development, Maintenance, API Integration.

Good communication & interpersonal skills.

TECHNICAL PROFICIENCY

Programming Language	PHP, Ajax, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery.
Server Programming	PHP.
Database	MySql
Operating System	Centos 7, Ubuntu, Windows XP, Windows 7.
Web Server	Apache, Nginx
IDE	phpStorm, Eclips, netbeans, geany, vim
Framework	Magento, Magento 2, Laravel, Codelgniter, Cakephp, Yii

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Born Group Private Limited.

May 2019 - PRESENT

Senior Software Developer

Job description:

Responsible for development and customization.

KENSIUM SOLUTION Pvt. Ltd.

(March 2019 - May 2019)

Senior Magento Developer

Job description:

Responsible for Preparation of Cloud ERP Extension optimization & customization.

BLUEHORSE SOFTWARE SOLUTION Pvt. Ltd. (DEC 2011 - FEB 2017)

Senior PHP Developer

Job description:

Responsible for Preparation of Web Based Applications Development.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

Year of Passing	Description
2011	Bachelor In Computer Application (BCA) from Medinipur College under Vidyasagar University and secured an aggregate of 61.4%.
2008	XII from Maher B.M High School (W.B.C.S.E) and secured an aggregate of 66.8%.
2006	X from Maher B.M High School (W.B.B.S.E) and secured an aggregate of 60.8%.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth : 29-September-1988

Gender : Male

Father's name : Sukumar Mondal

Mother tongue : Bengali Nationality : Indian Marital Status : Single

Languages : Hindi, English, Bengali

Permanent address : Vill-Bural, P.O-Barjagu, P.S-Sabang, Dist-Paschim Medinipur, 721144.

DECLARATION

I do hereby declare that the particulars of information and facts stated herein above are true, correct and complete to the best of my knowledge and belief.

SUPRAVAT MONDAL